Contact

rspataru9@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rspataru9 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Linux MySQL Databases

Roman Spataru

GIS Specialist

Copenhagen, Capital Region, Denmark

Summary

GIS specialist, networks, programming and databases. Abilities to work with technical documentation, to prioritize workload and meet expectations.

Specialties: Programming abilities: C#, UML, C/C++, Visual Studio, SQL, Pascal, Delphi, VB.NET, Unix Shell (C, Bash), C++ Builder, Excellent OOP skills, multithreading programming

Web Programming: HTML/ XHTML, ASP.NET, Web Services, CSS, XML/DTD/Schema/XPath/XSLT, Java script, DOM, Ajax, PHP

DBMS: MS SQL2000/2005, Access, ADO.NET, MySQL

OS: Red-Hat Linux, FreeBSD, Windows

Network: Ethernet LAN design/debugging, OSI model, TCP/IP protocol stack, Sniffing, Wi-fi, Optical Network

Experience

World Health Organization 2 years 8 months

Geographic Information System Specialist and Data Manager August 2021 - Present (1 year 3 months)

Data Manager

March 2020 - August 2021 (1 year 6 months)

I have volunteered for a temporary assigned to International Health Regulation (IHR) on emergency response for COVID19 since beginning of March 2020.

UN City Copenhagen Software Engineer July 2014 - March 2020 (5 years 9 months) World Health Organization 5 years 11 months

Temporary acting as Data Manager May 2013 - July 2014 (1 year 3 months)

System Engineer
September 2008 - May 2013 (4 years 9 months)

Capevo Ltd System Developer July 2008 - September 2008 (3 months)

Endava Ltd Software Engineer May 2007 - May 2008 (1 year 1 month)

Department "Network and Internet".

Academy of Economic Studies from Moldova System Administrator November 2002 - May 2007 (4 years 7 months) Maintain the Network System Routing, optics network, Wi-fi.

Also Install and support of servers: FTP(file server), MAIL, DNS, WEB, Proxy internet service, SQL, MRTG(network traffic statistics) on BSD OS(operation system), Linux OS and Windows 2003 OS.

RENAM Association Network Engineer 2003 - 2005 (2 years)

Education

Lund University

Degree of Master in Geographical Information Science, Geographic Information Science and Cartography · (January 2019)

Academy of Economic Studies from Moldova
Higher Education, IT, Programming, Database, Network, Economics,
Accounting · (2002 - 2007)